To sink or swim 生き残るために
Dog eat dog world だと言い聞かせる
What went wrong?
Surviving with the fate, it’s 弱肉強食
Face a world that our wisdom only will tell me
What went wrong
I’ve paid my dues, I’ve sold my soul
So tell me what is left for me
When I’ve given up everything
ねえ　取り替えてたんだろう
どの景色を見ても　何も感じなかったよ
ねえ　考え直しても
あの景色を求めていた　僕は無感情だろう
ねえ　取り替えてたんだろう
どの景色を見ても　何も感じなかったよ
ねえ　考え直しても
あの景色を求めていた　僕は無感情だろう
真実の見えない世界
善と悪のバランスを保ち
殺すか殺されるかの
ちっぽけな世界なのかよ？
おい、誰か答えてみてくれよ
It’s just like a burning torch in the storm
Like a little flower blooming in the home
強く確かな意志を掲げ
ときに優しくあればいい
I’m missing you
滲む景色に膝を抱き
胸をはせる時
Listen to me, sail away again
未開の海に回路を照らす願い
繋いだ声は　答えのない世界へと
帆を揺らす You’re not alone
ただ荒波をゆけ
その闇に向け